const impossible = [
  {
    question: "Nephophobia is a fear of __:",
    answers: {
      a: "Heights",
      b: "Clouds",
      c: "Glass",
      d: "Textbooks"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question:
      'Shiro Cosmetics sells an eyeshadow called "__ Raking Leaves on a Brisk October Afternoon"',
    answers: {
      a: "Shrine Maiden",
      b: "Angry Mother",
      c: "Arctic Monkeys",
      d: "Nic Cage"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
  },
  {
    question: '"Hatoful Boyfriend" is a visual novel where you can date __:',
    answers: {
      a: "Demons",
      b: "Centaurs",
      c: "Pigeons",
      d: "Teachers"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "Ouagadougou is the capital city of which African country?",
    answers: {
      a: "Chad",
      b: "Burkina Faso",
      c: "Eritrea",
      d: "Djibouti"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Code of Hammurabi decreed that bartenders who watered down beer would __:",
    answers: {
      a: "Be executed.",
      b: "Lose all tips.",
      c: "Do well in life.",
      d: "Make enemies."
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "Who invented scissors?",
    answers: {
      a: "Thomas Edison",
      b: "Marvin Haywood",
      c: "Leonardo Da Vinci",
      d: "George Foreman"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "Oxford University is older than __:",
    answers: {
      a: "Babylonia",
      b: "The Tower of London",
      c: "The Aztec Empire",
      d: "The Great Wall of China"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "The name for the shape of Pringle's can is __",
    answers: {
      a: "Cylinder",
      b: "Hyperbolic Paraboloid",
      c: "Dodecahedron",
      d: "Nonagon"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "George Clooney played the voice of __:",
    answers: {
      a: 'Simba from "Lion King"',
      b: 'Peter Griffin from "Family Guy"',
      c: 'Stuffy from "Doc McStuffins"',
      d: 'Sparky from "South Park"'
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "It is illegal to hunt camels in __:",
    answers: {
      a: "Pakistan",
      b: "New Mexico",
      c: "Kenya",
      d: "Arizona"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
  }
];
